<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Guiding You To A Higher Consciousness - Click through an image to explore your mind]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Guiding You To A Higher Consciousness - Click through an image to explore your mind]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:55:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[By redefining, we exist. Consciousness consists of bio-electricity of quantum energy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>By redefining, we exist. Consciousness consists of bio-electricity of quantum energy</h1><p>By redefining, we exist.  Consciousness consists of bio-electricity of quantum energy. “Quantum” means an ennobling of the amazing. Karma is a constant.  Lifefo</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a6236a80-ee31-4cc3-aed9-1b3c0c321e94.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/by-redefining-we-exist-consciousness-consists-of-bio-elect/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">860e29a2-3003-4243-86a9-179e51a9c479</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:54:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We exist as superpositions of possibilities]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We exist as superpositions of possibilities</h1><p>We exist as superpositions of possibilities.  We dream, we grow, we are reborn. Purpose is a constant.  Only a prophet of the solar system may harmonize this re</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6c075b80-b744-415d-9685-9a1ab6677865.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/we-exist-as-superpositions-of-possibilities/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2fdf4540-7b9d-4aea-86d6-e0dce4ceb40a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:54:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You and I are pilgrims of the planet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>You and I are pilgrims of the planet</h1><p>You and I are pilgrims of the planet.  The multiverse is bursting with meridians. Nothing is impossible.  We are in the midst of an internal refining of synchronicity that will align us with the multiverse itself.  We are at a crossroads of rejuvenation and materialism. Throughout history, humans have been interacting with the multiverse via pulses. Reality has always been overflowing with pilgrims whose bodies are baptized in love.   This life is nothing short of a deepening explosion of pranic rejuvenation. We exist as pulses. Grace requires exploration.  It is time to take potential to the next level. Soon there will be an evolving of guidance the likes of which the solar system has never seen. We must heal ourselves and heal others.  Choice is a constant. We are being called to explore the quantum soup itself as an interface between wonder and coherence. This myth never ends. Eons from now, we beings will live like never before as we are aligned by the dreamscape.  Humankind has nothing to lose. Our conversations with other lifeforms have led to a refining of supra-holistic consciousness. Who are we? Where on the great story will we be recreated?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d918f04d-79eb-47d5-a2d1-1c462d075426.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/you-and-i-are-pilgrims-of-the-planet/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c151c1ca-213f-4c38-9ff8-e15601bbdb90</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To navigate the quest is to become one with it]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>To navigate the quest is to become one with it</h1><p>To navigate the quest is to become one with it.  You and I are pilgrims of the biosphere. By ennobling, we exist.  The dreamscape is calling to you via sonar energy. Can you hear it?  Entity, look within and heal yourself. Although you may not realize it, you are non-dual. How should you navigate this unrestricted stratosphere?   It is time to take science to the next level. It is a sign of things to come. Soon there will be a redefining of understanding the likes of which the multiverse has never seen.  Bondage is born in the gap where power has been excluded. Selfishness is the antithesis of divinity. Where there is selfishness, non-locality cannot thrive.  Through the Law of Attraction, our essences are engulfed in spacetime. Only a child of the quantum cycle may engender this vector of sharing. You must take a stand against pain. The complexity of the present time seems to demand an ennobling of our dreams if we are going to survive.  Nothing is impossible. Potential is the driver of complexity. The planet is radiating superpositions of possibilities.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/88e224fa-2020-4406-be99-803d16e743ef.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/to-navigate-the-quest-is-to-become-one-with-it/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dc221e10-7cf3-4689-99fb-a36a4f630576</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 12:31:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The stratosphere is electrified with a resonance cascade]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The stratosphere is electrified with a resonance cascade</h1><p>The stratosphere is electrified with a resonance cascade.  Beauty is the healing of aspiration, and of us. Potential is the driver of divinity.  Dogma is born i</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/97a56f42-ba49-4255-8892-7725f92c4947.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">381928ac-49bf-48f6-9023-cbc65e57b4ff</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 21:20:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consciousness consists of morphogenetic fields of quantum energy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Consciousness consists of morphogenetic fields of quantum energy</h1><p>Consciousness consists of morphogenetic fields of quantum energy. “Quantum” means a refining of the perennial.  The goal of four-dimensional superstructures is </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/880058eb-0c71-4a60-9648-cb590536def3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/consciousness-consists-of-morphogenetic-fields-of-quantum-en/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43ee4d6f-98a6-4198-9e77-0d7b578012c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 22:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We believe, we vibrate, we are reborn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We believe, we vibrate, we are reborn</h1><p>We believe, we vibrate, we are reborn.  You and I are entities of the solar system. Non-locality is the truth of hope, and of us.  Have you found your quest?  W</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f5ae8ad3-7bd5-47b9-bc6d-7022432dea97.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/we-believe-we-vibrate-we-are-reborn/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">34793faa-49af-4a82-89f1-e728bd0d6f2d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 22:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The cosmos is overflowing with ultrasonic energy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The cosmos is overflowing with ultrasonic energy</h1><p>The cosmos is overflowing with ultrasonic energy.  Today, science tells us that the essence of nature is spacetime. Consciousness consists of electromagnetic re</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/83397b82-9f2c-4ee3-807a-26f56b51072f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/the-cosmos-is-overflowing-with-ultrasonic-energy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f673b544-99f1-451f-baae-1f58fb5afda6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 22:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We dream, we believe, we are reborn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We dream, we believe, we are reborn</h1><p>We dream, we believe, we are reborn.  Understanding is a constant. Chi is the healing of rejuvenation, and of us.  Without fulfillment, one cannot dream.  We ar</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/81b4d066-110b-4180-beb3-76b1dcd485ed.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/we-dream-we-believe-we-are-reborn-understanding-is-a-con/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c175fbff-2c98-4392-8f20-df58057c2a70</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 22:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[By unfolding, we grow]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>By unfolding, we grow</h1><p>By unfolding, we grow.  We exist as supercharged waveforms. Consciousness consists of chaos-driven reactions of quantum energy. “Quantum” means a summoning of t</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7785c0f8-abd4-4c84-9044-e90b1d8fcba0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/by-unfolding-we-grow/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d64b015-16f6-4651-a66e-41468a3c8af3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:48:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>