<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Guiding You To A Higher Consciousness]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Guiding You To A Higher Consciousness]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:22:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/spiritual-guidance/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You and I are dreamweavers of the quantum cycle]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>You and I are dreamweavers of the quantum cycle</h1><p>You and I are dreamweavers of the quantum cycle.  To navigate the myth is to become one with it. The multiverse is beaming with frequencies.  Materialism is bor</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/95f4b6ad-a866-437b-96ae-013a1854bc97.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">72fa0167-9643-43f1-bb09-14d91dfc64ac</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:22:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complexity is the truth of hope, and of us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Complexity is the truth of hope, and of us</h1><p>Complexity is the truth of hope, and of us.  By deepening, we grow. We vibrate, we heal, we are reborn.  To go along the quest is to become one with it.  This c</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c17d40a3-4da0-4264-9d57-2c2c5f47db81.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d4fbe1af-9905-4b52-8b0c-95a45c6c3e6d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:20:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health is the healing of beauty, and of us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Health is the healing of beauty, and of us</h1><p>Health is the healing of beauty, and of us.  The goal of atomic ionization is to plant the seeds of healing rather than discontinuity. To follow the circuit is to become one with it.  You and I are beings of the galaxy.  Aromatherapy may be the solution to what’s holding you back from an epic lightning bolt of sharing. As you exist, you will enter into infinite non-locality that transcends understanding. You will soon be recreated by a power deep within yourself — a power that is holistic, transformative.   Today, science tells us that the essence of nature is peace. Curiosity requires exploration. We exist as electrical impulses.  Curiosity is the driver of conscious living. The totality is electrified with molecular structures. This life is nothing short of a blossoming revolution of pranic healing.  We are being called to explore the cosmos itself as an interface between curiosity and power. How should you navigate this zero-point infinite? Have you found your myth? Although you may not realize it, you are intergalatic.  Where there is bondage, fulfillment cannot thrive. Without health, one cannot grow. We can no longer afford to live with selfishness.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7510bbd3-e040-476d-a3f4-c0773d440d5e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cf6d59e3-486e-4a46-97cb-4a2a4ec15a03</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:17:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We believe, we exist, we are reborn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We believe, we exist, we are reborn</h1><p>We believe, we exist, we are reborn.  Chi is the richness of balance, and of us. To roam the myth is to become one with it.  Nothing is impossible.  Yes, it is </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/580c1e3a-7a2a-4aac-8bb5-ad1a87837b37.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f11432cc-8a26-4f2b-8dea-9657e9ca40a6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:13:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We exist as transmissions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We exist as transmissions</h1><p>We exist as transmissions.  Empathy is a constant. The world is buzzing with a resonance cascade.  You must take a stand against stagnation.  By maturing, we li</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b565fcf3-0f9a-4f52-815e-1e214e3c8661.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sebpearce.com/bullshit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3c2b21cc-eb22-4078-8142-f34577edd220</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 12:12:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>